https://www.cati.com/company/privacy-policy/

blog
cati@cati.com
888-308-2284Computer Aided Technology, Inc would like to thank you for visiting our website. We know many visitors have questions regarding the privacy of their interactions on our website. We hope this privacy policy statement will answer any questions you may have, but if it does not, please feel free to contact us at the email address or postal address shown below.Visiting our Website In general, you can visit the Computer Aided Technology website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself, such as your name, phone number, or postal or email address.Occasionally you may be asked to give us more specific information about yourself, such as when you register for a seminar or other event, respond to a survey or register for training. Supplying such information to us is optional, but you may be unable to complete certain transactions without giving such information.The Use of Personal Information Computer Aided Technology may use the personal information you provide us for a variety of purposes, including registration, authentication, and marketing purposes. We may use the information to inform you of special offers, upgrades and other products and services that may be of interest to you.You may use the Computer Aided Technology web site to email your resume to Computer Aided Technology. Computer Aided Technology will keep your resume strictly confidential and use it only in the context of filling employment opportunities at Computer Aided Technology.Computer Aided Technology products and Services are not marketed to children under the age of 13 years old and Computer Aided Technology does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 years old.If you do not wish to receive information about additional Computer Aided Technology products or services or those of its partners and other companies, please let us know (see the contact information below) and we will respect your wishes.Computer Aided Technology stores the personal data of customers and web site visitors indefinitely and may maintain and process such information directly or indirectly in one or more databases. If you provide personal information to Computer Aided Technology, you agree and consent to Computer Aided Technology’s storage and usage of this information anywhere that Computer Aided Technology and its affiliates maintain offices for the purposes described above. Computer Aided Technology takes reasonable precautions to protect the personal data from loss, unauthorized access, alteration, misuse, and disclosure.The Computer Aided Technology website may contain information about third parties and/or links to other websites. Computer Aided Technology is not responsible for the accuracy of such information and for the privacy practices, security, or more generally, the content of these websites.Updating Personal Information and “Opting Out” Computer Aided Technology wants to ensure that the information it collects is accurate. Please notify us of any change to your address, phone number, email address or other information by sending us an email message at cati@cati.com or by notifying us in writing atComputer Aided Technology, Inc 165 Arlington Heights Rd, Suite 101 Buffalo Grove, IL 60089If at any time you wish to “opt out” of receiving information from Computer Aided Technology, please notify us by sending us an email or written message at the addresses shown above. Please note that due to lead times on certain mailings and other contacts, you may continue to receive contacts for a period following your “opt out” notification.Changes to this Policy Computer Aided Technology may change this policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted to this site, so we encourage you to review our privacy policy from time to time. ©
Computer Aided Technology, LLC
Sitemap  •  Privacy Policy
x
Search
TopProducts & SolutionsServices3D Printing3D ScanningTrainingSupportEventsIndustriesCompany
Search
